Samantha Sloan

4740 West 125th Avenue
Broomfield, Colorado 80020
(303) 489-1303
samantha.sloan31@gmail.com
www.linkedin.com/in/slsloan | www.github.com/slsloan

SUMMARY

Detail-oriented professional with 9+ years of experience and a proven knowledge of customer satisfaction, report building for team efficiency, and in-depth knowledge of the specific softwares that is used. Curious individual with a passion for technologies specifically in software development and database management. Looking to utilize technical skills in a new environment.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Windows/Mac platforms	Databases (MySQL,
MS Office Suite (Advanced	MongoDB)
Excel)	Deployment (Heroku, Git)
Google	PHP/Laravel
Drive/Docs/Slides/Sheets	Quality Assurance (Writing
Salesforce	Tests)
Slack	Server Side Development
Computer Science applied to	(Node.js, Express, MERN Stack)
JavaScript	Final Cut X and Sony Vegas
Browser Based Technologies	Adobe Creative Suite
(HTML, CSS, JavaScript,	(Illustrator, Premiere,
jQuery)	Photoshop)

EXPERIENCE

Gusto, Denver, CO - Outbound Sales Representative

MARCH 2019 - PRESENT

- Makes a total of 85 dials a day to warm leads.
- Prioritizes incoming leads/accounts created when calling prospects.
- Utilizes the Sandler Sales Methodology to work with prospects on deciding whether or not they should move forward with Gusto as their Payroll, HR, and Benefits platform.
- Works cross-functionally with other teams to ensure that customer satisfaction is high.

Global Healthcare Exchange (GHX), Louisville, CO - Customer Support Analyst II

JULY 2018 - FEBRUARY 2019

- Identify, research, and resolve customer issues, questions, and concerns in a timely manner.
- Defined problems, collected data, and established facts to draw valid conclusions.
- Provide customers with product and service information.

- Complete call logs and reports.
- Use Salesforce to create and manage cases on customer issues, questions, or concerns

Hyland Hills Parks & Recreation District, Westminster, CO - Manager/Group Sales

AUGUST 2011 - AUGUST 2018

- Scheduling group events by phone and email, entering in a point-of-sale system.
- Event planning, setup, and hosting for private corporate and customer parties and customer appreciation events.
- Developed and enforced safety standards and procedures for food quality and sanitation purposes.
- Assisted Operation Manager with balancing, identifying and reconciling daily transactions.
- Payroll system timesheet entry and reporting.
- Recruited, interviewed, hired and trained employees on new procedures and requirements.
- Supervised up to 15 team members.
- Producer, cinematographer, and editor of training videos.

Vans a Division of VF Outdoor, Fort Collins, CO - Sales Lead

SEPTEMBER 2015 - AUGUST 2017

- Acted as manager-on-duty during management absences.
- Communicated sales goals to team members, provided motivation and feedback for sales associates to succeed in reaching sales goals.
- Directed training of new team members and mentored each to promote productivity, accuracy and friendly service.
- Maintained knowledge of current sales and promotions, policies regarding payment and exchanges.
- Completed setup, breakdown and product preparation for promotional displays and in-store demonstrations.
- Generated brand awareness and positive product impressions to increase sales.
- Up-sold and cross-sold products effectively, driving sales and increasing revenue.

EDUCATION

Denver University, Denver, CO - Certification in Full-Stack Development

MARCH 2020 - PRESENT

Colorado State University, Fort Collins, CO - BA - Hospitality Management

AUGUST 2013 - MAY 2017

Minor in Business Administration

Dean's List Fall 2015-Spring 2017